<root>
<doc>
  <docid>3</docid>
  <msgtext>From: guyd@austin.ibm.com (Guy Dawson) Subject: Re: IDE vs SCSI, DMA and detach Originator: guyd@pal500.austin.ibm.com Organization: IBM Austin Lines: 60 In article &lt;1993Apr19.034517.12820@julian.uwo.ca&gt;, wlsmith@valve.heart.rri.uwo.ca (Wayne Smith) writes: &gt; In article &lt;RICHK.93Apr15075248@gozer.grebyn.com&gt; richk@grebyn.com (Richard Krehbiel) writes: &gt; &gt;&gt; Can anyone explain in fairly simple terms why, if I get OS/2, I might &gt; &gt;&gt; need an SCSI controler rather than an IDE. Will performance suffer that &gt; &gt;&gt; much? For a 200MB or so drive? If I don't have a tape drive or CD-ROM? &gt; &gt;&gt; Any help would be appreciated. &gt; &gt; &gt;So, when you've got multi-tasking, you want to increase performance by &gt; &gt;increasing the amount of overlapping you do. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt;One way is with DMA or bus mastering. Either of these make it &gt; &gt;possible for I/O devices to move their data into and out of memory &gt; &gt;without interrupting the CPU. The alternative is for the CPU to move &gt; &gt;the data. There are several SCSI interface cards that allow DMA and &gt; &gt;bus mastering. &gt; ^^^^^^^^^^^^ &gt; How do you do bus-mastering on the ISA bus? &gt; &gt; &gt;IDE, however, is defined by the standard AT interface &gt; &gt;created for the IBM PC AT, which requires the CPU to move all the data &gt; &gt;bytes, with no DMA. &gt; &gt; If we're talking ISA (AT) bus here, then you can only have 1 DMA channel &gt; active at any one time, presumably transferring data from a single device. &gt; So even though you can have at least 7 devices on a SCSI bus, explain how &gt; all 7 of those devices can to DMA transfers through a single SCSI card &gt; to the ISA-AT bus at the same time. Think! It's the SCSI card doing the DMA transfers NOT the disks... The SCSI card can do DMA transfers containing data from any of the SCSI devices it is attached when it wants to. An important feature of SCSI is the ability to detach a device. This frees the SCSI bus for other devices. This is typically used in a multi-tasking OS to start transfers on several devices. While each device is seeking the data the bus is free for other commands and data transfers. When the devices are ready to transfer the data they can aquire the bus and send the data. On an IDE bus when you start a transfer the bus is busy until the disk has seeked the data and transfered it. This is typically a 10-20ms second lock out for other processes wanting the bus irrespective of transfer time. &gt; &gt; Also, I'm still trying to track down a copy of IBM's AT reference book, &gt; but from their PC technical manual (page 2-93): &gt; &gt; "The (FDD) adapter is buffered on the I.O bus and uses the System Board &gt; direct memory access (DMA) for record data transfers." &gt; I expect to see something similar for the PC-AT HDD adapter. &gt; So the lowly low-density original PC FDD card used DMA and the PC-AT &gt; HDD controller doesn't!?!? That makes real sense. -- -- ----------------------------------------------------------------------------- Guy Dawson - Hoskyns Group Plc. guyd@hoskyns.co.uk Tel Hoskyns UK - 71 251 2128 guyd@austin.ibm.com Tel IBM Austin USA - 512 838 3377</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>5653</docid>
  <msgtext>From: wb8foz@skybridge.SCL.CWRU.Edu (David Lesher) Subject: Re: What do Nuclear Site's Cooling Towers do? Organization: NRK Clinic for habitual NetNews abusers - Beltway Annex Lines: 19 Reply-To: wb8foz@skybridge.scl.cwru.edu (David Lesher) NNTP-Posting-Host: skybridge.scl.cwru.edu Others said: # &gt; Actually, fossil fuel plants run hotter than the usual # &gt;boiling-water reactor nuclear plants. (There's a gripe in the industry # &gt;that nuclear power uses 1900 vintage steam technology). So it's # &gt;more important in nuclear plants to get the cold end of the system # &gt;as cold as possible. Hence big cooling towers. When the utility gave up on that Cinnci, OH plant (Zimmer?) and announced they were going to convert it to a coal-fired scheme, the turbines were already in place, and they were the low-temp type. So the plan was: Install a SECOND set of high temp turbines, and feed the low-temp ones with the output of the new ones. Never saw anything more on this. Did they ever really build it? -- A host is a host from coast to coast..wb8foz@skybridge.scl.cwru.edu &amp; no one will talk to a host that's close............(301) 56-LINUX Unless the host (that isn't close).........................pob 1433 is busy, hung or dead....................................20915-1433</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>1127</docid>
  <msgtext>From: eabu500@orion.oac.uci.edu (Michael) Subject: Re: DeskWriter driver v3.1 problems Nntp-Posting-Host: dialin33611.slip.nts.uci.edu X-UserAgent: Nuntius v1.1.1d17 Organization: UC Irvine Lines: 12 X-XXMessage-ID: &lt;A7FFA003FB028ECA@dialin33611.slip.nts.uci.edu&gt; X-XXDate: Sun, 25 Apr 93 17:55:15 GMT In article &lt;87439@ut-emx.uucp&gt; Marc Bizer, mlbizer@bongo.cc.utexas.edu writes: &gt; &gt;Has it happened to anyone that while printing a beep is heard and a &gt;message is displayed of the sort "Such-and-such a window was closed &gt;because the Finder did not have enough memory"? Or am I the only one &gt;suffering from this delusion? &gt; --Marc Bizer This can be solved by going into your system folder and do a Get Info (command I) on the Finder and give it more memory.</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>3319</docid>
  <msgtext>From: kjenks@gothamcity.jsc.nasa.gov Subject: Space Station Redesign, JSC Alternative #4 Organization: NASA/JSC/GM2, Space Shuttle Program Office X-Newsreader: TIN [version 1.1 PL8] Lines: 71 I have 19 (2 MB worth!) uuencode'd GIF images contain charts outlining one of the many alternative Space Station designs being considered in Crystal City. Mr. Mark Holderman works down the hall from me, and can be reached for comment at (713) 483-1317, or via e-mail at mholderm@jscprofs.nasa.gov. Mark proposed this design, which he calls "Geode" ("rough on the outside, but a gem on the inside") or the "ET Strongback with integrated hab modules and centrifuge." As you can see from file geodeA.gif, it uses a Space Shuttle External Tank (ET) in place of much of the truss which is currently part of Space Station Freedom. The white track on the outside of the ET is used by the Station Remonte Manipulator System (SRMS) and by the Reaction Control System (RCS) pod. This allows the RCS pod to move along the track so that thrusting can occur near the center of gravity (CG) of the Station as the mass properties of the Station change during assembly. The inline module design allows the Shuttle to dock more easily because it can approach closer to the Station's CG and at a structurally strong part of the Station. In the current SSF design, docking forces are limited to 400 pounds, which seriously constrains the design of the docking system. The ET would have a hatch installed pre-flight, with little additional launch mass. We've always had the ability to put an ET into orbit (contrary to some rumors which have circulated here), but we've never had a reason to do it, while we have had some good reasons not to (performance penalties, control, debris generation, and eventual de-orbit and impact footprint). Once on-orbit, we would vent the residual H2. The ET insulation (SOFI) either a) erodes on-orbit from impact with atomic Oxygen, or b) stays where it is, and we deploy a Kevlar sheath around it to protect it and keep it from contaminating the local space environment. Option b) has the advantage of providing further micrometeor protection. The ET is incredibly strong (remember, it supports the whole stack during launch), and could serve as the nucleus for a much more ambitious design as budget permits. The white module at the end of ET contains a set of Control Moment Gyros to be used for attitude control, while the RCS will be used for gyro desaturation. The module also contains a de-orbit system which can be used at the end of the Station's life to perform a controlled de-orbit (so we don't kill any more kangaroos, like we did with Skylab). The centrifuge, which has the same volume as a hab module, could be used for long-term studies of the effects of lunar or martian gravity on humans. The centrifuge will be used as a momentum storage device for the whole attitude control system. The centrifuge is mounted on one of the modules, opposite the ET and the solar panels. This design uses most of the existing SSF designs for electrical, data and communication systems, getting leverage from the SSF work done to date. Mark proposed this design at Joe Shea's committee in Crystal City, and he reports that he was warmly received. However, the rumors I hear say that a design based on a wingless Space Shuttle Orbiter seems more likely. Please note that this text is my interpretation of Mark's design; you should see his notes in the GIF files. Instead of posting a 2 MB file to sci.space, I tried to post these for anon-FTP in ames.arc.nasa.gov, but it was out of storage space. I'll let you all know when I get that done. -- Ken Jenks, NASA/JSC/GM2, Space Shuttle Program Office kjenks@gothamcity.jsc.nasa.gov (713) 483-4368 "...Development of the space station is as inevitable as the rising of the sun." -- Wernher von Braun</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>8935</docid>
  <msgtext>Subject: Re: Ranger Fans????? From: kwolfer@eagle.wesleyan.edu Organization: Wesleyan University Nntp-Posting-Host: willet.wesleyan.edu Lines: 75 In article &lt;1993Apr22.171734.9534@alleg.edu&gt;, ballb@reis56.alleg.edu (Brett Ball) writes: &gt; In article &lt;1993Apr22.101356.1@eagle.wesleyan.edu&gt; writes: &gt;&gt; I for one am happy about the Ranger's hiring of Keenan. It's too bad &gt; that they &gt;&gt; didn't hire him when Smith fired Nielsen, maybe he could of staightened &gt; out the &gt;&gt; babies on this team and made the playoffs. What this team needs is a &gt; little &gt;&gt; fire under their butts!! &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; Reading through most of these hockey news I don't see many Ranger fans &gt; writing. &gt;&gt; I'm new to this system and a big hockey fan and a long suffering(1940) &gt; Ranger &gt;&gt; fan. But remember suffering builds character!! &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; I have some final questions about the way the team was handled in that &gt; last &gt;&gt; dreadful stretch. &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; 1. Knowing they needed offensive help from the blueline, why didn't we &gt; see Mike &gt;&gt; Hurlbut, who played pretty well when he was called up when Leetch first &gt; went &gt;&gt; down? &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; 2. Why????!!!!! is Joe Kocur playing every night? He is not Bob Probert &gt; who is &gt;&gt; tough but also can play. &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; 3. How come Paul Broten is relegated to street clothes for the end of &gt; the &gt;&gt; season. At least he plays with some heart and character, draws &gt; penalties and &gt;&gt; plays 110% when he's on the ice. Was he in the doghouse for some &gt; reason? &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; 4. Joe Cirella?????!!!! Enough said! &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; Ranger fans may be suffering but we're some of the most loyal, unlike &gt; Islander &gt;&gt; fans who only show up when the team wins. &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; As far as the Stanley Cup goes I think there's only one team that can &gt; test &gt;&gt; Pittsburgh and that's Detroit. This would be the most entertaining and &gt; hard &gt;&gt; fought series. Mario is amazing! &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; Kurt &gt; &gt; I think Joe Kocus should play every night. He is a big physical guy, and &gt; he gets the fans into the game with some big hits. (both checks and &gt; fists) Its a big advantage to get the crowd going. Plus, he helps &gt; protect the other players. Notice there are very few fights when Kocur is &gt; on the ice unless he is it. I have seen people start to go after essa &gt; Tikkanen, only to go slinking away when Kocur steps in. I think he is big &gt; asset, but should be third line, and special situation only play. &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt;This is fast becoming a game without the goons. I admit Kocur may get the fans into the game but surely they would rather see Broten taking a pass from Kovalev and scoring a breakaway goal to put the Rangers up 3 (magic #) goals in the third period, rather than seeing Kocur take another stupid penalty and the Rangers giving up another powerplay goal! The Rangers need another top flight center who can take the pressure off Messier and the first line. Nemchinov is a perfect third line center. So who goes Beezer or Richter? Kurt</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>2552</docid>
  <msgtext>From: gtoal@gtoal.com (Graham Toal) Subject: Re: Do we need the clipper for cheap security? Lines: 21 : From: pmetzger@snark.shearson.com (Perry E. Metzger) : Indeed, were it not for the government doing everything possible to : stop them, Qualcomm would have designed strong encryption right in to : the CDMA cellular phone system they are pioneering. Were it not for : the NSA and company, cheap encryption systems would be everywhere. As : it is, they try every trick in the book to stop it. Had it not been : for them, I'm sure cheap secure phones would be out right now. In the UK, it's impossible to get approval to attach any crypto device to the phone network. (Anything that plugs in to our BT phone sockets must be approved - for some reason crypto devices just never are...) I was wondering some time ago how big a market there was for good old- fashion acoustic coupler technology to build a secure phone :-) ... is it possible to mask out all the real voice well enough so that none of it strays into the mouthpiece? Perhaps a well-sealed coupler attachment that was as well blocked as possible, then a white noise generator on the outside to muffle any real speech? G</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>18441</docid>
  <msgtext>From: lmtra@uts.amdahl.com (Leon Traister) Subject: Celery and Hypertension Organization: Amdahl Corporation, Sunnyvale CA Lines: 11 Somewhere or other I read that when a person of Chinese heritage was told that he had high blood pressure he responded by eating celery (sorry, I don't recall the "dosage"). Apparently this is supposed to work in reducing hypertension. Can anyone out there verify this? And if it does work, does anyone know the appropriate amounts and possible side-effects? Thanks, Leon Traister (lmtra@uts.amdahl.com)</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>294</docid>
  <msgtext>From: channui@austin.ibm.com (Christopher Chan-Nui) Subject: Re: Two pointing devices in one COM-port? Reply-To: channui@austin.ibm.com Organization: IBM Austin X-Newsreader: TIN [version 1.1 PL9] Lines: 22 Bob Davis (sonny@trantor.harris-atd.com) wrote: : In article &lt;C4tKGM.1v6@unix.portal.com&gt;, wil@shell.portal.com (Ville V Walveranta) writes: : |&gt; : |&gt; Is there any way to connect two pointing devices to one serial : |&gt; port? I haven't tried this but I believe they would interfere : |&gt; with each other (?) even if only one at a time would be used. : Just get an A-B switch for RS232. Look in Computer Shopper. : They are available fairly cheap. They allow switching between two : serial devices on a single port. Unfortunately the poster wants to use an internal and an external modem so a switch isn't going to help them. If you aren't using your com ports for anything else, just define them on different com ports. Define your internal modem to be say, com1, and your external modem to be com3. You really shouldn't have to worry about interrupt conflicts since you won't be using both modems at the same time :). --- Christopher Chan-Nui | Investment in reliability will increase until it channui@austin.ibm.com | exceeds the probable cost of errors, or until someone #include &lt;disclaimer.h&gt; | insists on getting some useful work done.</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>16515</docid>
  <msgtext>From: ronaldm@extro.ucc.su.OZ.AU (Ron Mastus) Subject: Problem with Adaptec 1542B SCSI and Jumbo Tape Drive Summary: Problem getting Jumbo Tape drive and Adaptec SCSI working together Keywords: SCSI CMS Jumbo Adaptec 1542B Tape Nntp-Posting-Host: extro.ucc.su.oz.au Organization: Sydney University Computing Service, Sydney, NSW, Australia Lines: 39 Hi, I've just replaced my existing DTC SCSI controller with an Adaptec 1542B, and am now having trouble restoring from a Jumbo 250 tape drive. I had no trouble installing the Adaptec and DOS recognises both the SCSI drive and an existing IDE drive - however when I went to restore the backups from the Jumbo tape I found that it was extremely slow (estimated time 3 mins actual time 15 min!) I have no trouble restoring from the same tape to the IDE drive. I seem to remember reading that some settings had to be changed to enable the Jumbo drive and the Adaptec to work together but I can't find any mention of it in the manuals. My system config is: i486DX/33 4Mb Adaptec 1542B running 180Mb Fujitsu SCSI IDE Controller running 200Mb IDE Jumbo 250 running off floppy controller on IDE Any help would be appreciated Thanks, Ron. (ronaldm@extro.ucc.su.oz.au) ------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Ron Mastus ronaldm@extro.ucc.su.oz.au 41 Mariposa Rd Phone +61 2 ???-???? (work) Bilgola Plateau 2107 +61 2 918-8152 (home) Australia -- ------------------------------------------------------------------------------- Ron Mastus ronaldm@extro.ucc.su.oz.au 41 Mariposa Rd Phone +61 2 ???-???? (work) Bilgola Plateau 2107</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>10724</docid>
  <msgtext>From: jmd@cube.handheld.com (Jim De Arras) Subject: Re: CLINTON JOINS LIST OF GENOCIDAL SOCIALIST LEADERS Organization: Hand Held Products, Inc. Lines: 112 Distribution: world NNTP-Posting-Host: dale.handheld.com In article &lt;1993Apr26.174819.13707@starbase.trincoll.edu&gt; () writes: &gt; In article &lt;1ra5i9INNd4g@clem.handheld.com&gt;, jmd@cube.handheld.com (Jim De &gt; Arras) wrote: &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; In article &lt;1993Apr23.153005.8237@starbase.trincoll.edu&gt; () writes: &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; I've yet to meet a group of Baptists who were stockpiling Cambell's soup &gt; &gt; &gt; and M-16's/AR-15's and banging/marrying thirteen yuear olds. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; I don't recall saying Baptists do any of that. Though I suppose some do. And &gt; &gt; none of them are listed in the dictionary as characteristics of a cult. My &gt; &gt; mother stockpiled Campbells soup when it was on sale. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; You're a sorry &gt; &gt; &gt; son of a bitch if you can't draw a distinction between these two things. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; You are an intolerent, foul-mouthed human. You sound like you are ready to &gt; &gt; join the KKK or neo-nazis, with a narrow mind like yours. &gt; &gt; Fuck YOU. My paternal grandparents died in Oswiecym (Aushwitz in the native &gt; tongue, for all of you pseudo-historically literate people). And Bejing = Peking, who cares about native tongue, as long as we all understand each other. &gt; I would &gt; suggest you'd have to search long and hard to find someone with more &gt; diffuse sensibilities. Oh, not more than a few feet, I wouldn't think. I'm sorry IF your paternal grandparents died in Oswiecym or Aushwitz, which is easier to say than prove, but if so, the lesson they paid thier lives for was wasted on you. &gt; Just tootin' my own horn. You are the expert. I often feel compelled to brag about the circumstances of my grandparent's death. 8-} &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; People like you cheapen our constitution by using it to defend sociopaths &gt; &gt; &gt; who aren't deserved of it. Get a life and chill on the paranoia. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; I don't care about *cults*. There's no language problem here. My problem is &gt; with religious fanatics (claiming to be God is just a *little bit* &gt; unsettling) stockpiling several years' supply of canned foods and enough &gt; weapons to hold off a company (not to mention the ATF, which %&amp;^#ed up in &gt; the first place) and talking about how they're going to "take care" of all &gt; of the "unbelievers." But granted, up to that moment, he'd done nothing &gt; wrong. I recognize and respect that. &gt; &gt; Then the ATF discovers he doesn't have proper permits for some of his &gt; purchases and failed to pay some taxes on them. &gt; A BATF offense, if true. &gt; Then several parents come forward and demand that previous charges of child &gt; abuse be refiled. There have been interviews with some parents whose &gt; children were in the compound at some point. These parents claimed &gt; psychological and sexual abuse. The childrens' statements supported these &gt; charges. A LOCAL offense, if true. Totally outside the BATF's domain. &gt; &gt; Was it a 'no-knock?' I really haven't heard anything on that. But clearly &gt; he was not just another guy minding his own business. Hell, give them all &gt; the guns in the world if they don't bother anyone. But he was a scary sort, &gt; don't you think? I didn't know the man. Just what the TV chose to tell me. &gt; The sort of person you'd want your daughter to date? I thought there were prejudicial undertones here. I would trust my daughter's judgement. &gt; I &gt; didn't think so. Reason number one to doubt the legal statements made by &gt; some of the survivors. (Note that some of them were made by his 'guard,' &gt; well-[hesitate to say expertly] trained killers). I don't believe either side blindly. &gt; &gt; Then he fired on the ATF. That's not just a little mistake, or some &gt; red-white-and blue American defending his home against Big Brother. IF they fired first, without announcing in a beleivable way who they were ( I can pound on your door and claim to be the police, will you just lay down and take it if I do?), then he could be justified in firing on the ATF in self-defense. &gt; That &gt; shit doesn't fly. Anyone with his background that will shoot and kill &gt; Federal Law Enforcement officials is not some good citizen whose crusade &gt; enjoys our support. He's a loose cannon. Just my opinion... "His background"? What law has he been convicted of breaking in the past? &gt; &gt; joe.kusmierczak@mail.trincoll.edu Jim -- jmd@handheld.com ------------------------------------------------------------------------------- "I'm always rethinking that. There's never been a day when I haven't rethought that. But I can't do that by myself." Bill Clinton 6 April 93 "If I were an American, as I am an Englishman, while a foreign troop was landed in my country, I never would lay down my arms,-never--never--never!" WILLIAM PITT, EARL OF CHATHAM 1708-1778 18 Nov. 1777</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>15000</docid>
  <msgtext>From: Fil.Sapienza@med.umich.edu (Fil Sapienza) Subject: Re: Why do people become atheists? Organization: University of Michigan Hospitals Lines: 24 In article &lt;May.7.01.09.44.1993.14556@athos.rutgers.edu&gt; maxwell c muir, muirm@argon.gas.organpipe.uug.arizona.edu writes: &gt;of Faith (if you want to know, I feel that faith is intellectually &gt;dishonest). I'd appreciate some support for this statement. I'm not sure it really makes sense to me. &gt;The ambiguity of religious beliefs, an unwillingness to take &gt;Pascal's Wager, I've heard this frequently - what exactly is Pascal's wager? &gt; Do I sound "broken" to you? I don't know. You point out that your mother's treatment upset you, and see inconsistencies in various religions. I'm not sure if that constitutes broken-ness or not. It certainly consititutes disillusionment. -- Filipp Sapienza Department of Technology Services University of Michigan Hospitals - Surgery Fil.Sapienza@med.umich.edu</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>3176</docid>
  <msgtext>From: caf@omen.UUCP (Chuck Forsberg WA7KGX) Subject: Re: My New Diet --&gt; IT WORKS GREAT !!!! Organization: Omen Technology INC, Portland Rain Forest Lines: 33 In article &lt;19687@pitt.UUCP&gt; geb@cs.pitt.edu (Gordon Banks) writes: &gt; &gt;In article &lt;1993Apr13.093300.29529@omen.UUCP&gt; caf@omen.UUCP (Chuck Forsberg WA7KGX) writes: &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt;"Weight rebound" is a term used in the medical literature on &gt;&gt;obesity to denote weight regain beyond what was lost in a diet &gt;&gt;cycle. There are any number of terms which mean one thing to &gt; &gt;Can you provide a reference to substantiate that gaining back &gt;the lost weight does not constitute "weight rebound" until it &gt;exceeds the starting weight? Or is this oral tradition that &gt;is shared only among you obesity researchers? Not one, but two: Obesity in Europe 88, proceedings of the 1st European Congress on Obesity Annals of NY Acad. Sci. 1987 &gt;-- &gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------- &gt;Gordon Banks N3JXP | "Skepticism is the chastity of the intellect, and &gt;geb@cadre.dsl.pitt.edu | it is shameful to surrender it too soon." &gt;---------------------------------------------------------------------------- -- Chuck Forsberg WA7KGX ...!tektronix!reed!omen!caf Author of YMODEM, ZMODEM, Professional-YAM, ZCOMM, and DSZ Omen Technology Inc "The High Reliability Software" 17505-V NW Sauvie IS RD Portland OR 97231 503-621-3406</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>6697</docid>
  <msgtext>From: mckay@alcor.concordia.ca (John McKay) Subject: Re: Math?? (Was US govt &amp; Technolgy Investment Keywords: science? Nntp-Posting-Host: alcor.concordia.ca Organization: Concordia University, Montreal, Canada Lines: 21 mwilson@ncratl.AtlantaGA.NCR.COM (Mark Wilson) writes: &gt;|&gt;Report called it The Science of Order, but that's probably pomposity. &gt;|It is, however, now somewhat of an experimental science with the exploration &gt;|of fractals, strange attractors, and artificial life. Whether important &gt;|insights will be gained from these experiments is unknown, but it does &gt;|tend to change the shape of what has mostly been viewed as an abstract &gt;|deductive field. &gt;How do you do experiments in mathematics? Well ... Have a look at a new journal: Journal of Experimental Mathematics It has several Fields medallists on its editorial board. You want to knwo more? Try Klaus Peters in Boston or David Epstein at Warwick . -- Deep ideas are simple. Odd groups are even. Even simples are not.</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>8577</docid>
  <msgtext>From: nagle@netcom.com (John Nagle) Subject: Re: FBI Director's Statement on Waco Standoff Organization: NETCOM On-line Communication Services (408 241-9760 guest) Lines: 34 ndallen@r-node.hub.org (Nigel Allen) writes: &gt; FBI Director's Statement On Waco Standoff &gt; "I had hoped to be making a very different statement this evening. &gt;After very careful planning and extensive preparation we all thought &gt;that today's efforts by the FBI to bring the Branch Davidians out of &gt;their compound would result in the peaceful resolution of the &gt;stand-off or at least meaningful negotiation. &gt; "Instead, we are faced with devastation and death. However, I &gt;have no question that our plan was correct and was conducted with &gt;extreme professionalism and care. I applaud the restraint shown by &gt;agents in the face of life-threatening gunfire, and I thank them for &gt;risking their lives to try to end this peacefully. I have only the &gt;greatest admiration for the courage and professionalism of all &gt;involved." "I have no question that our plan was correct?" Months to get ready, unlimited funds, knowledge of a threatened mass suicide by fire, and no fire trucks on hand? This is "extreme professionalism and care?" I can understand the first screwed-up raid by the BATF. They underestimated the opposition, which happens. But not this one. The FBI had their first team in place, massive resources, ample time for planning and bringing up any specialized equipment or people necessary. They still botched it. The FBI Director and the FBI SAC in overall charge should resign, or be fired for incompetence. I don't blame Reno or Clinton. They gave the FBI clear orders: don't go in unless you can do it without casualties; if you can't do that, wait it out. Those were reasonable orders. The FBI said they could pull off a tactical solution, and they couldn't. John Nagle</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>13432</docid>
  <msgtext>From: catone@compstat.wharton.upenn.edu (Tony Catone) Subject: Re: 17" Monitors &lt;C5GEH5.n1D@utdallas.edu&gt; Organization: University of Pennsylvania Lines: 14 Nntp-Posting-Host: compstat.wharton.upenn.edu In-reply-to: goyal@utdallas.edu's message of 14 Apr 93 03:17:28 GMT In article &lt;C5GEH5.n1D@utdallas.edu&gt; goyal@utdallas.edu (MOHIT K GOYAL) writes: Oh yeah, I just read in another newsgroup that the T560i uses a high quality Trinitron tube than is in most monitors.(the Sony 1604S for example) and this is where the extra cost comes from. It is also where the high bandwidth comes from, and the fantastic image, and the large image size, etc, etc... It's also where the two annoying lines across the screen (one a third down, the other two thirds down) come from. - Tony catone@compstat.wharton.upenn.edu</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>14398</docid>
  <msgtext>From: burge@qdeck.com (Bill Burge) Subject: Re: DOS 6.0 Organization: Quarterdeck Office Systems, Santa Monica CA Distribution: na Lines: 22 In article &lt;4903@eastman.UUCP&gt; lrxi00@icts01.Kodak.COM (James Nonnemacher) writes: &gt;Is there enough experience out in netland with DOS 6.0 that anyone could make some comments on whether &gt;or not it's a worthwhile upgrade? Any problems with hardware compatibility or any bugs been found? &gt; &gt;One thing I wonder about is the disk doubler included with DOS 6.0. Is there any possiblity that if &gt;the disk double .exe file gets corrupted your disk would be unreadable? How would one recover from &gt;such an event? The file that would be a problem is DBLSPACE.BIN, not .EXE. /\_/\ ARF!! (0 0) +==========================----oOO--(_)--OOo----============================+ \ Bill Burge burge@qdeck.com / ^--- "and his dog Spot" / \ Problem Resolution &amp; Prevention \ BBS - (310) 314-3227 (N-8-1) / \ Quarterdeck Office Systems / FAX - (310) 314-3217 / \ \ QFAX- (310) 314-3214 / \ Tech Support - support@qdeck.com / (This is an automated "request / \ Gen'l Info - info@qdeck.com \ FAX" system, call it from the / \ CompuServe - GO QUARTERDECK / handset on your FAX) / +==================================+========================================+</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>18827</docid>
  <msgtext>From: starowl@rahul.net (Michael D. Adams) Subject: Re: New Study Out On Gay Percentage Nntp-Posting-Host: bolero Reply-To: starowl@rahul.net Organization: D Service Actuarial Consulting X-Newsreader: TIN [version 1.1 PL8] Lines: 26 On 21 Apr 93 00:07:20 GMT, Theodore A. Kaldis observed: : as010b@uhura.cc.rochester.edu (some caifone) writes: : &gt; because if she heard : Thankfully, you got the gender right. For I am not a deviant. Bigots aren't classified as deviants? How sad. : &gt; how disparaging you are towards political minorities, : Sexual deviants do not comprise a "political minorit[y]". So, what's this I hear about a March on Washington...assuming you are still considering homosexuality and bisexuality as subsets of "sexual deviants?" : &gt; and if she had any shred of self-respect, she'd be out the door. : I only associate with girls who do indeed have self-respect. I trust that many self-respecting *women* might take some sort of offense to your use of the term "girls" in the above sentence. -- Michael D. Adams (starowl@a2i.rahul.net) Enterprise, Alabama "Always listen to experts. They'll tell you what can't be done, and why. Then do it." -- Lazarus Long (Robert Heinlein)</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>16638</docid>
  <msgtext>From: husak@ux1.cso.uiuc.edu (Stephen R. Husak ) Subject: Tape Drive Problems Article-I.D.: ux1.C52szz.489 Organization: University of Illinois at Urbana Lines: 17 Please reply via e-mail since this is job related: I have a Colorado Jumbo back-up system at one of my places of employment and it has eaten two tapes by winding the tape off the spool. Is there an easy fix or is the tape drive fried? Does it simply need cleaning? Any and all comments will be appreciated! Stephen Husak -- "What am I trying to do, what am I trying to say, I'm not trying to tell you anything you didn't know when you woke up today..." - Depeche Mode "Nothing" MUSIC FOR THE MASSES -= Stephen R. Husak - husak@ux1.cso.uiuc.edu - Univerisity of Illinois</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>17691</docid>
  <msgtext>From: hardy@esdd460a.erim.org (Russ Hardy) Subject: Mary and Idols Organization: Environmental Research Institute of Michigan, Ann Arbor, Michigan Lines: 78 I have been studying the Bible now for about a year. I love it, but I am not very familiar with the different denominations, or traditions, or common beliefs of various christian groups. I have heard various people (outside this news group) describe *idols* such as power, money, material possessions etc. These things are worshiped in some sense I suppose, but I never really gave idols much thought. Until now... I have been reading the postings in this news group (which I just found a few days ago), and I have a question... First, I'm not trying to question anyone's belief or try to push my views on anyone else (I haven't been at this long enough to have any views other than I cannot get to heaven by being good, I must understand that Christ bore my sins on the cross so that I could be saved and I need to repent, i.e. realize that every time I sin, I might as well stick a sharp stick in Christ's side because He took the punishment for my sins, when He died on the cross). In my studies, Mary never really comes up. I know who she is, but that's about it. It seems to me that a statue of Mary could be considered an idol? Do people pray to statues of Mary? It sounds like educated christians (more educated than myself I'm sure) believe Mary was sinless? Wow... I hoped to spend the summer convincing myself (one way or the other) about Tongues (I'm reading "Charismatic Chaos"). I guess I'll study Tongues in parallel with reading this news group. Any help you can give me will be appreciated. ------------------------------------------- [I don't think the issue is so much that people are more educated than you (though it may well be that they are), as that they come from a different tradition than yours. This is a discussion between Catholics and Protestants. Catholics generally believe that Mary was sinless. Protestants do not. The issue comes down to different sources of authority. Protestants generally limit themselves to the Bible as a source of doctrine. Since this isn't in the Bible (except in passages that no one would understand in this way if they didn't already believe it), Protestants don't accept it. Catholics see continuing revelation through the Church, though they believe the results are consistent with the Bible. I interpret your posting, not as a call for yet another argument about whether the Catholic Marian devotions are idolatry (an argument I am not prepared to see newed here), but as a sign of being interested in learning about traditions other than your own. Catholics are of course a major one, but by no means the only one. I generally consider the major traditions to be Catholic, Orthodox, and various subsets of Protestantism. Within Protestantism, it's a matter of how finely you want to cut things. These days I think the major division is between those who accept Biblical inerrancy and those who don't. There are also a number of major historical traditions, but in recent decades distinctions are tending to blur. I'd identify the major Protestant traditions as: Lutheran, Reformed, Anglican (they're sort of halfway between Catholic and Protestant), Wesleyan, Baptist, Holiness, Pentecostal, Church of Christ But there are a number of others. Historical distinctions tend not to be so important among the liberal churches anymore, and I think current trends in society and the Church are also tending to make conservatives seen themselves as allies from a general "evangelical" perspective. But differences among these various traditions are still quite marked. I think the best introduction to these issues is to read a good book on church history. Anyone who wants to understand the church really needs to understand how we got where we are now. A church history will normally show you where each of these traditions came from, and give a feeling for their nature. Unfortunately I'm away from my library at the moment, so I don't have anything specific to recommend. --clh]</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>8772</docid>
  <msgtext>From: estel@cs.vu.nl (Stel E) Subject: W32/TSENG card &amp; other VLB cards... (please) Organization: Fac. Wiskunde &amp; Informatica, VU, Amsterdam Lines: 30 Hai, In a few days I'm going to buy a new motherboard with local-bus(ses). It comes with a Cirrus Logic VLB card which has 2Mb RAM onboard. It can do true-color but I don't know what type of card it is. I read that Cirrus Logic cards aren't exactly the fastes around. My old system had a TSENG 4000. I was pretty pleased with it, so I consider buying a W32/TSENG card. I'd like to know a few things: - How is the speed/performance in DOS/Windows/Unix/OS/2 Graphics &amp; Text (also compared to S3 cards for example) - What resolutions (including no. of colors) does it support (text &amp; graphics) - How many RAM can be installed and what type of RAM - System Compatibility with old TSENG 4000 - Support in software If anyone has any experience with this card (good or bad) I'd like to know. If you have a better alternative than the W32 please tell me about it. For the people in Holland: Kan iemand me misschien vertellen waar de W32 in Nederland te verkrijg is? Het liefst in de omgeving van Amsterdam! Thanks in advance, Erik Stel (estel@cs.vu.nl)</msgtext>
</doc>
</root>
