<root>
<doc>
  <docid>13029</docid>
  <msgtext>From: uni@acs.bu.edu (Shaen Bernhardt) Subject: Re: What the clipper nay-sayers sound like to me. Distribution: na Organization: Boston University, Boston, MA, USA Lines: 60 In article &lt;1qsvfcINNq9v@dns1.NMSU.Edu&gt; amolitor@moink.nmsu.edu (Andrew Molitor) writes: &gt; &gt; The following is available in some FTP archive somewhere, I insert &gt;my comments liberally throughout this demonic memo of Big Brotherdom: &gt; &gt;&gt; White House Announcement on Screw Thread Standards &gt;&gt; -------------------------------------------------- &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt; This is to announce that the American National Standards &gt;&gt;Institute (or whatever it is) has been given the authority to define &gt;&gt;standard dimensions for screw threads. &gt; &gt; Look! This is clearly the first step toward outlawing our &gt; own screw thread specifications. If this madness isn't fought, &gt; tooth and nail, every step of the way, it'll be a crime to use &gt; screw threads other than those our Fearless Leaders so *graciously* &gt; define for us. [Sarcastic text deleted, No value judgement implied] &gt; Screw you, Bill Clinton! You and your totalitarianist thugs! &gt; &gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------ &gt;amolitor@nmsu.edu | finger for PGST personal screw thread pitch, or &gt;Screw Threads | see the screw thread servers. &gt;must be freed! | &gt;------------------------------------------------------------------------ At first I was going to complain that your analogy was completely irrelevant. But then I remembered something. Remember that move to get the U.S. to the metric system all those years ago? As far as I know we were supposed to be there by now. The government sold it as better for the people, easier to be in tune with the rest of the world. They had decided it was for our own good. Then, when the plan was released, it soon became apparant that the government were a bunch 'o' thickies. Think about it, change all the railroad track widths, signs, screws, abolish the old regime. At the cost of millions of dollars. Your point is well taken. You think there is nothing to worry about, you could care less who designs your cryptography, any more than who designs your screws or the system of measurement you use. Sit back, that's right, just relax, we'll take care of all your needs Mr. Molitor. -- uni@acs.bu.edu -&gt; Public Keys by finger and/or request Public Key Archives: &lt;pgp-public-keys@pgp.iastate.edu&gt; Sovereignty is the sign of a brutal past.&lt;&gt;Fight Clinton's Wiretap Chip! DF610670F2467B99 97DE2B5C3749148C &lt;&gt; Crypto is not a Crime! Ask me how!</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>13591</docid>
  <msgtext>From: dbm0000@tm0006.lerc.nasa.gov (David B. Mckissock) Subject: Re: Space Station Redesign Chief Resigns for Health Reasons Organization: NASA Lewis Research Center / Cleveland, Ohio Lines: 30 Distribution: world NNTP-Posting-Host: tm0006.lerc.nasa.gov News-Software: VAX/VMS VNEWS 1.41 In article &lt;C5xuGL.Jow@skates.gsfc.nasa.gov&gt;, xrcjd@mudpuppy.gsfc.nasa.gov (Charles J. Divine) writes... &gt;Writer Kathy Sawyer reported in today's Washington Post that Joseph Shea, the &gt;head of the space station redesign has resigned for health reasons. &gt; &gt;Shea was hospitalized shortly after his selection in February. He returned &gt;yesterday to lead the formal presentation to the independent White House panel. &gt;Shea's presentation was rambling and almost inaudible. I missed the presentations given in the morning session (when Shea gave his "rambling and almost inaudible" presentation), but I did attend the afternoon session. The meeting was in a small conference room. The speaker was wired with a mike, and there were microphones on the table for the panel members to use. Peons (like me) sat in a foyer outside the conference room, and watched the presentations on closed circuit TV. In general, the sound system was fair to poor, and some of the other speakers (like the committee member from the Italian Space Agency) also were "almost inaudible." Shea didn't "lead the formal presentation," in the sense of running or guiding the presentation. He didn't even attend the afternoon session. Vest ran the show (President of MIT, the chair of the advisory panel). &gt; &gt;Shea's deputy, former astronaut Bryan O'Connor, will take over the effort. Note that O'Connor has been running the day-to-day operations of the of the redesign team since Shea got sick (which was immediately after the panel was formed).</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>16841</docid>
  <msgtext>From: smb@research.att.com (Steven Bellovin) Subject: Clipper chip -- technical details Organization: AT&amp;T Bell Laboratories Lines: 121 I received the following two notes from Martin Hellman with details on how Clipper will work. They are posted with his permission. The implications of some details are fascinating. ------- Date: Sat, 17 Apr 93 23:05:23 PDT From: "Martin Hellman" &lt;hellman@isl.stanford.edu&gt; To: (a long list of recipients) Subject: Clipper Chip Most of you have seen the announcement in Friday's NY Times, etc. about NIST (National Institute of Standards &amp; Technology) announcing the "Clipper Chip" crypto device. Several messges on the net have asked for more technical details, and some have been laboring under understandable misunderstandings given the lack of details in the news articles. So here to help out is your friendly NSA link: me. I was somewhat surprised Friday to get a call from the Agency which supplied many of the missing details. I was told the info was public, so here it is (the cc of this to Dennis Branstad at NIST is mostly as a double check on my facts since I assume he is aware of all this; please let me know if I have anything wrong): The Clipper Chip will have a secret crypto algorithm embedded in Silicon. Each chip will have two secret, 80-bit keys. One will be the same for all chips (ie a system-wide key) and the other will be unit specific. I don't know what NIST and NSA will call them, but I will call them the system key SK and unit key UK in this message. The IC will be designed to be extremely difficult to reverse so that the system key can be kept secret. (Aside: It is clear that they also want to keep the algorithm secret and, in my opinion, it may be as much for that as this stated purpose.) The unit key will be generated as the XOR of two 80-bit random numbers K1 and K2 (UK=K1+K2) which will be kept by the two escrow authorities. Who these escrow authorities will be is still to be decided by the Attorney General, but it was stressed to me that they will NOT be NSA or law enforcement agencies, that they must be parties acceptable to the users of the system as unbiased. When a law enforcement agency gets a court order, they will present it to these two escrow authorities and receive K1 and K2, thereby allowing access to the unit key UK. In addition to the system key, each user will get to choose his or her own key and change it as often as desired. Call this key plain old K. When a message is to be sent it will first be encrypted under K, then K will be encrypted under the unit key UK, and the serial number of the unit added to produce a three part message which will then be encrypted under the system key SK producing E{ E[M; K], E[K; UK], serial number; SK} When a court order obtains K1 and K2, and thence K, the law enforcement agency will use SK to decrypt all information flowing on the suspected link [Aside: It is my guess that they may do this constantly on all links, with or without a court order, since it is almost impossible to tell which links over which a message will flow.] This gives the agency access to E[M; K], E[K; UK], serial number in the above message. They then check the serial number of the unit and see if it is on the "watch list" for which they have a court order. If so, they will decrypt E[K; UK] to obtain K, and then decrypt E[M; K] to obtain M. I am still in the process of assessing this scheme, so please do not take the above as any kind of endorsement of the proposed scheme. All I am trying to do is help all of us assess the scheme more knowledgably. But I will say that the need for just one court order worries me. I would feel more comfortable (though not necessarily comfortable!) if two separate court orders were needed, one per escrow authority. While no explanation is needed, the following story adds some color: In researching some ideas that Silvio Micali and I have been kicking around, I spoke with Gerald Gunther, the constitutional law expert here at Stanford and he related the following story: When Edward Levi became Pres. Ford's attorney general (right after Watergate), he was visited by an FBI agent asking for "the wiretap authorizations." When Levy asked for the details so he could review the cases as required by law, the agent told him that his predecessors just turned over 40-50 blank, signed forms every time. Levi did not comply and changed the system, but the lesson is clear: No single person or authority should have the power to authorize wiretaps (or worse yet, divulging of personal keys). Sometimes he or she will be an Edward Levi and sometimes a John Mitchell. Martin Hellman ---- Date: Sun, 18 Apr 93 11:41:42 PDT From: "Martin Hellman" &lt;hellman@isl.stanford.edu&gt; To: smb@research.att.com Subject: Re: Clipper Chip It is fine to post my previous message to sci.crypt if you also post this message with it in which: 1. I ask recipients to be sparse in their requesting further info from me or asking for comments on specific questions. By this posting I apologize for any messages I am unable to respond to. (I already spend too much time answering too much e-mail and am particularly overloaded this week with other responsibilities.) 2. I note a probably correction sent to me by Dorothy Denning. She met with the person from NSA that I talked with by phone, so her understanding is likely to better than mine on this point: Where I said the transmitted info is E{ E[M; K], E[K; UK], serial number; SK} she says the message is not double encrypted. The system key (or family key as she was told it is called) only encrypts the serial number or the serial number and the encrypted unit key. This is not a major difference, but I thought it should be mentioned and thank her for bringing it to my attention. It makes more sense since it cuts down on encryption computation overhead.</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>615</docid>
  <msgtext>From: st1my@rosie.uh.edu (Stich, Christian E.) Subject: Motorola XC68882RC33 and RC50 Organization: University of Houston Lines: 17 Distribution: world NNTP-Posting-Host: rosie.uh.edu Keywords: Motorola, FPU, 68882, 68030, 33/50 MHz, problems (FPU exception) News-Software: VAX/VMS VNEWS 1.41 I just installed a Motorola XC68882RC50 FPU in an Amiga A2630 board (25 MHz 68030 + 68882 with capability to clock the FPU separately). Previously a MC68882RC25 was installed and everything was working perfectly. Now the systems displays a yellow screen (indicating a exception) when it check for the presence/type of FPU. When I reinstall an MC68882RC25 the system works fine, but with the XC68882 even at 25 MHz it does not work. The designer of the board mentioned that putting a pullup resistor on data_strobe (470 Ohm) might help, but that didn't change anything. Does anybody have some suggestions what I could do? Does this look like a CPU-FPU communications problem or is the particular chip dead (it is a pull, not new)? Moreover, the place I bought it from is sending me an XC68882RC33. I thought that the 68882RC33 were labeled MC not XC (for not finalized mask design). Are there any MC68882RC33? Thanks Christian</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>6851</docid>
  <msgtext>From: davet@interceptor.cds.tek.com (Dave Tharp CDS) Subject: Re: Rejetting carbs.. Keywords: air pump Distribution: na Organization: Tektronix - Colorado Data Systems, Englewood, CO Lines: 58 In article &lt;jburney.734756216@hydra.nodc.noaa.gov&gt; jburney@hydra.nodc.noaa.gov (Jeff Burney) writes: &gt; &gt;If we are only talking about 4-stroke (I think I can understand exhaust &gt;pulse affect in a 2-stroke), the intake valve is closed on the &gt;exhaust stroke and the gas is pushed out by the cyclinder. I guess &gt;there is some gas compression that may affect the amount pushed out &gt;but the limiting factor seems to be the header pipe and not the &gt;canister. Meaning: would gases "so far" down the line (the canister) &gt;really have an effect on the exhaust stroke? Do the gases really &gt;compress that much? For discussion purposes, I will ignore dynamic effects like pulses in the exhaust pipe, and try to paint a useful mental picture. 1. Unless an engine is supercharged, the pressure available to force air into the intake tract is _atmospheric_. At the time the intake valve is opened, the pressure differential available to move air is only the difference between the combustion chamber pressure (left over after the exhaust stroke) and atmospheric. As the piston decends on the intake stroke, combustion chamber pressure is decreased, allowing atmospheric pressure to move more air into the intake tract. At no time does the pressure ever become "negative", or even approach a good vacuum. 2. At the time of the exhaust valve closing, the pressure in the combustion chamber is essentially the pressure of the exhaust system up to the first major flow restriction (the muffler). Note that the volume of gas that must flow through the exhaust is much larger than the volume that must flow through the intake, because of the temperature difference and the products of combustion. 3. In the last 6-8 years, the Japanese manufacturers have started paying attention to exhaust and intake tuning, in pursuit of almighty horsepower. At this point in time, on high-performance bikes, substitution of an aftermarket free-flow air filter will have almost zero affect on performance, because the stock intake system flows very well anyway. Substitution of an aftermarket exhaust system will make very little difference, unless (in general) the new exhaust system is _much_ louder than the stocker. 4. On older bikes, exhaust back-pressure was the dominating factor. If free-flowing air filters were substituted, very little difference was noted, unless a free-flowing exhaust system was installed as well. 5. In general, an engine can be visualized as an air pump. At any given RPM, anything that will cause the engine to pump more air, be it on the intake or exhaust side, will cause it to produce more horsepower. Pumping more air will require recalibration (rejetting) of the carburetor. ----------------------------------------------------------------------------- | Dave Tharp | DoD #0751 | "You can't wear out | | davet@interceptor.CDS.TEK.COM | MRA #151 | an Indian Scout, | | '88 K75S '48 Indian Chief | AHRMA #751 | Or its brother the Chief.| | '75 R90S(#151) '72 TR-2B(#751) | AMA #524737 | They're built like rocks | | '65 R50/2/Velorex '57 NSU Max | | to take the knocks, | | 1936 BMW R12 | (Compulsive | It's the Harleys that | | My employer has no idea. | Joiner) | give you grief." | -----------------------------------------------------------------------------</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>14378</docid>
  <msgtext>From: rhaller@ns.uoregon.edu (Rich Haller) Subject: Resound Hearing aids (and others) Organization: University of Oregon Lines: 31 Distribution: world NNTP-Posting-Host: rhaller.cc.uoregon.edu I have a fairly severe high frequency hearing loss. A recent rough test showed a gently sloping loss to 10-20db down at 1000cps. Then it falls off a cliff to 70-80dbs down from 1500cps on. This type of loss is difficult to fit. I am currently using some old siemens behind the ear aids which keep me roughly functional, but leave a lot to be desired. Recently I had an opportunity to test the Widex Q8 behind the ear aids for several weeks. These have four independent programs which are intended to be customized for different hearing situations and can be reprogramed. I found them to be a definite improvement over my current aids and was about to go ahead with them until another local outfit advertised a free trial of another programmable system called ReSound. Unfortunately I was only able to try the ReSound aids in their office for about 30 minutes and I couldn't compare them 'head to head' with the Widex. Nevertheless, it did appear to me that they were superior and I was impressed by what I was able to read about the theory behind them which I will give in a separate posting. They also carry the Widex aids and had one patient (presumably wealthy) who decided to go ahead and get the ReSound even though he had purchased the Widex only 6 months ago. The problem is that the ReSound aids are about twice as expensive as the Widex and other programmable aids. I could take a trip to Europe on the difference! Being a lover of bargains and hating to spend money, I am having a hard time persuading myself to go with the ReSounds. I would appreciate any opinions on this and other hearing aids and projections about when and if I might see improvements in technology that aren't quite so expensive. -Rich Haller &lt;rhaller@ns.uoregon.edu&gt; University of Oregon, Eugene, OR, USA</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>13939</docid>
  <msgtext>From: roger@crux.Princeton.EDU (Roger Lustig) Subject: Re: ALL-TIME BEST PLAYERS Originator: news@nimaster Nntp-Posting-Host: crux.princeton.edu Reply-To: roger@astro.princeton.edu (Roger Lustig) Organization: Princeton University Lines: 49 In article &lt;1993Apr22.204633.1@woods.ulowell.edu&gt; poiriera@woods.ulowell.edu writes: &gt; This chatting about the best player of all time is pointless. You &gt;can't compare players from different era's. Of course you can. You just have to be careful about what conclusions you draw. &gt;If you will notice the best &gt;pitchers (stat wise were in the 20's and 30's) and the best all around hitters &gt;probably came from the 40's to 60's. Huh? The 20's and 30's were the *worst* decades for great pitching. Grove, Vance, Dean, and not a whole lot else. As for the best all-around hitters, stat-wise, Ruth, Gehrig, Foxx, Greenberg, Hornsby, Cobb, etc. all played before the 40's. Stat-wise, the 60's were a graveyard for hitters. &gt;Now we have a great number of great &gt;pitchers and an equally great number of great hitters and fielders. (Also, How do you know? Which ones do you consider great? &gt;about fielding, the gloves were much smaller than they are now in the early &gt;years of baseball) Maybe a hitter like Sheffield with the .330 BA, 30hr, and &gt;100+ RBI(Even though it was probably a fluke year) can be compared to a Mantle &gt;because the pitching Sheffield faces is faster and not to mention better. The So? Sheffield also has better shoes. More time between pitches. You can run the comparison, but there are *lots* of things to take into account. &gt;same could be said for Frank Thomas who is said to be the best hitter since Ted &gt;Williams, although Frank's defense does suck. Well, can we compare them or can't we? &gt; All I am saying is that you can't compare players from different era's, &gt;if you want a best player try choosing best players from different era's. That Why? We can compare players to the *standard* of their era; and we can keep in mind era-to-era differences without throwing up our hands in despair. &gt;way there is reasonable basis for comparison. You haven't shown us what's *un*reasonable about the MAntle-Sheffield comparison that you yourself did. Roger</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>14018</docid>
  <msgtext>From: plastic@ecr.mu.oz.au (Jason_Brinsley LEE) Subject: 25 words or less.... Organization: Computer Science, University of Melbourne, Australia Lines: 13 Everywhere we see and hear about christianity (due to its evangalistic nature). Witnessing, spreading the gospel, etc. But what I want to know is... "Why should I (or anyone else) become a Christian?" (In twenty five words or less). Zeros and Ones will take us there.... peace. plastic. 1993. [We've had enough discussions about evidence recently that it would probably be best to respond via email. --clh]</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>3266</docid>
  <msgtext>From: doyle+@pitt.edu (Howard R Doyle) Subject: Re: Persistent vs Chronic Organization: Pittsburgh Transplant Institute Lines: 31 In article &lt;10587@blue.cis.pitt.edu&gt; kxgst1+@pitt.edu (Kenneth Gilbert) writes: &gt; &gt;Seriously though, I wonder how someone with CPH would end up getting a &gt;biopsy in the first place? My understanding (and feel free to correct me) &gt;is that the enzymes are at worst mildly elevated, with overall normal &gt;hepatic function. I would think that the only clue might be a history of &gt;prior HepB infection and a positive HepB-sAg. Or is it indeed on a &gt;continuum with CAH, and the distinction merely one of pathology and &gt;prognosis, but otherwise identical clinical features? &gt; Chronic persistent hepatitis is usually diagnosed when someone does a liver biopsy on a patient that has persistently elevated serum transaminases months after a bout of acute viral hepatitis, or when someone is found to have persistently elevated transaminases on routine screening tests. The degree of elevation (in the serum transaminases) can be trivial, or as much as ten times normal. Other blood chemistries are usually normal. As a rule, patients with CPH have no clinical signs of liver disease. Chronic active hepatitis can also be asymptomatic or minimally symptomatic, at least initially, and that's why it's important to tell them apart by means of a biopsy. The patient with CPH only needs to be reassured. The patient with CAH needs to be treated. ====================================== Howard Doyle doyle+@pitt.edu</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>4256</docid>
  <msgtext>From: norris@athena.mit.edu (Richard A Chonak) Subject: Boston Church Organization: unus orbis orans Lines: 14 (Dear Moderator: Would you add this to the BCC faq?) In case there are any ex-members of the "Boston Church of Christ" looking for a support organization, here's the number of "BostonEX" in Burlington, MA: 617-272-1955. -------- s.r.c readers in New England may be interested in seeing a series of news reports about the BCC in the 6 pm nightly news on Channel 5 (WCVB, Boston), for the next few days (starting Wed, 5/19). For viewers outside the Boston area, the same telecasts will also be aired on the "New England Cable News" channel at 8 pm.</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>5666</docid>
  <msgtext>From: mzhao@magnus.acs.ohio-state.edu (Min Zhao) Subject: cheap hard drives for your PC/XT Nntp-Posting-Host: top.magnus.acs.ohio-state.edu Organization: The Ohio State University Lines: 16 I have a few the original IBM 10Mb harddisks for sale. They are actually Seagate's ST412, MFM, full height, has the IBM logo and black face plate. Each disk is checked and formatted with DOS 6.0. It can be doubled to 20Mb or so with dblspace or stacker if you so desire. Have the original IBM foam fitted boxies and anti-static bags. I am not sure if they were ever used, but each drive that is sent out will be quarenteed in good working order. $30 each plus shipping cost, (about $5), If you have one of those old IBM XT or PCs, this is for you ! It's cheaper than a floppy drive !</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>15641</docid>
  <msgtext>From: Clinton-HQ@Campaign92.Org (The White House) Subject: CLINTON: Press Briefing by George Stephanopoulos 4.20.93 Organization: MIT Artificial Intelligence Lab Lines: 874 NNTP-Posting-Host: life.ai.mit.edu THE WHITE HOUSE Office of the Press Secretary _____________________________________________________________________ For Immediate Release April 20, 1993 PRESS BRIEFING BY GEORGE STEPHANOPOULOS The Briefing Room 12:36 P.M. EDT MR. STEPHANOPOULOS: As you know, the President is going to come out at 1:15 p.m. With your indulgence, I think what we'd like to do is have the President award the National Teacher's Award first and then have the teacher leave, or whatever, and then he'll make a statement on Waco and take a couple questions. So if we can just hold off going live and all that until that's done, it probably will work out a lot better. Q If you'll give us the time. That's the problem. Q We've got a two-minute warning problem. MR. STEPHANOPOULOS: Yes, it is a problem. It's about 1:15 p.m. Q The teacher would walk off and then -- MR. STEPHANOPOULOS: I think that's -- I'm just trying to work this out here. I think that's the best way to handle it. Q Can I ask you a series of questions about the way the President handled the notifications yesterday? MR. STEPHANOPOULOS: Sure. Q Did you, for instance, talk to the Justice Department about who would come out and discuss what had happened in Waco and whether it should be the Attorney General or the President? MR. STEPHANOPOULOS: Why don't we just take a step even farther back from that and look at the whole sequence of events on the contact between the Justice Department and the White House. As you know and as we've said, the President spoke with the Attorney General on Sunday, Sunday afternoon. They had a good discussion, about 15 minutes. The Attorney General informed the President of what she wanted to do. He raised no objections. Obviously, she had the implicit authority from the President to go forward. He raised no objections. She went forward. THE PRESS: Thank you . END 1:03 P.M. EDT #60-04/20</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>6970</docid>
  <msgtext>From: luriem@alleg.edu(Michael Lurie) The Liberalizer Subject: Winfield has Re: 200 SBs &amp; 200 HRs Organization: Allegheny College Lines: 47 In article &lt;mjones.735584681@fenway&gt; mjones@fenway.aix.kingston.ibm.com (Mike Jones) writes: &gt; dans@fore.csd.sgi.com (Dan Steinman) writes: &gt; &gt;Last night on the Giants/Mets radio broadcast Hank and Ted were &gt; &gt;discussing the fact that there were only 16 players who had ever hit &gt; &gt;200 homeruns and stolen 200 bases in their career (while HoJo was &gt; &gt;batting). Anyone have a list? Not as easy as it sounds to come up &gt; &gt;with all of them. I couldn't. Mays, Mantle, Aaron, Henderson, Morgan, &gt; &gt;Bonds (Dad), ??? Frank Robinson? Molitor? Yount? Guessing now. I'd &gt; &gt;be interested to see the whole list. &gt; &gt; First, please watch your line lengths. Not everyone has autowrap. &gt; Second, Franklin to the rescue! Here's the list: &gt; Player HR SB &gt; Aaron 755 240 &gt; Mays 660 338 &gt; FRobinson 586 204 &gt; RJackson 563 228 &gt; Winfield 406 216 * &gt; Dawson 377 304 * &gt; Baylor 338 285 &gt; BoBonds 332 461 &gt; Wynn 291 225 &gt; Strawberry 280 201 * &gt; Morgan 268 689 &gt; Pinson 256 309 &gt; Yount 235 247 * &gt; KGibson 208 253 * &gt; Sandberg 205 297 * &gt; &gt; Players marked with an * are still active; numbers through 1991. That's only &gt; 15; the 16th is probably Rickey Henderson, who was listed at 184 HR, 994 &gt; SB or George Brett, listed as 186 SB, 291 HR. &gt; &gt; The surprises? Probably Reggie, Bayor, and Wynn for steals. Maybe Morgan (to &gt; a lot of people) for homers. I was kind of surprised to realize that &gt; Sandberg has that many steals, though I wasn't surprised that the number was &gt; &gt;200. &gt; &gt; Mike Jones | AIX High-End Development | mjones@donald.aix.kingston.ibm.com &gt; &gt; Dreams are real while they last. Can we say more of life? &gt; - Havelock Ellis</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>5811</docid>
  <msgtext>From: george.marengo@filebank.cts.com (George Marengo) Subject: Re: head-to-head win and Distribution: world Organization: The File Bank BBS - Fallbrook, CA 619-728-4318 Reply-To: george.marengo@filebank.cts.com (George Marengo) Lines: 15 JG&gt; After this fall, I believe IBM no longer has any rights to JG&gt; view Microsoft code. After that, the only way to maintain JG&gt; some sort of compatibility is to reverse-engineer. Would JG&gt; you want to reverse-engineer an OLE2 application? Don't they retain Windows NT OEM status? If so, that gives them NT source code, and since Windows is headed toward NT... (Win32S, Win32C) * SLMR 2.1a * --T-A+G-L-I+N-E--+M-E-A+S-U-R+I-N-G+--G-A+U-G-E-- ---- *--------------------------------------------------------------------------* | The File Bank BBS - 619-728-4318 - PCBoard v.14.5a/E10 - USR HST &amp; DS | | 8 nodes / RIME / Internet / Largest Clipper file collection in the world | *--------------------------------------------------------------------------*</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>649</docid>
  <msgtext>From: vzhivov@superior.carleton.ca (Vladimir Zhivov) Subject: Re: Individual Winners (WAS: Re: WHERE ARE THE DOUBTERS NOW? HMM?) Organization: Carleton University Lines: 52 In &lt;1993Apr15.170226.11074@cci632.cci.com&gt; dwk@cci632.cci.com (Dave Kehrer) writes: &gt;Well, since you mentioned it... &gt;In article &lt;1993Apr12.142028.6300@jarvis.csri.toronto.edu&gt;, migod@turing.toronto.edu (Mike Godfrey) writes: &gt; &gt;&gt; Chelios the Norris, &gt;If you asked me 30 days ago, I'd agree with you. I now give the nod to &gt;Raymond Bourque; his play took off the same time the B's did. Chelios &gt;gets a close second... How about Kevin Hatcher? Scored roughly 35 goals, plays 30 minutes a game. &gt;&gt; dunno who wins the Vezina, but I suspect not Potvin. &gt; &gt;Barrasso finally gets his due, in a close one over Eddie the Eagle... That's really sad when two second-rate goalies (Barasso and Belfour) are the main contenders for the Vezina. Call me crazy, but how about Tommy Soderstrom - five shutouts for a 6th place team that doesn't really play defense. It's really unfortunate that the better goalies in the league (McLean, Essensa, Vernon) had unspectacular years. BTW, if you are going to award the Norris on the basis of the last 30 days, why not give the Vezina to Moog? He has been the best goalie over the past month. &gt;&gt; Coach of the year is tricky: Burns did the most with the least raw talent, &gt;&gt; King did a good job but the Flames clearly underachieved last year, Brian &gt;&gt; Sutter has done exceptionally well in his first year with a new team, ditto &gt;&gt; Demers, Page has been blessed by the ripening and acquisition of young &gt;&gt; talent, Darryl Sutter is having a good year for a rookie coach, Berry made &gt;&gt; the best of a bad situation, Terry Crisp worked minor miracles, and Bowman &gt;&gt; was Bowman. I'd pick Burns, but I'm mildly biased. &gt;In *your* case, that bias is acceptable :-)... Mine shows with the Norris pick, &gt;so we're even... &gt;I'm impressed with what all the coaches you mentioned did, but my pick would be &gt;Al Arbour. Not too many folks thought the Isles would be in the playoffs, let &gt;alone contend for 3rd in their division... Granted that they *did* have a little &gt;help from their cousins on Broadway... :-) &gt;And I like the Islanders about as much as I like mowing my lawn... Arbour or King. Burns will probably win, since playoffs aren't taken into consideration - he's OK in the regular season, but I'm not sure if he's beaten anyone other than Hartford in the playoffs. - Vlad the Impaler</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>3598</docid>
  <msgtext>From: mccoy@gothamcity.jsc.nasa.gov (Daniel McCoy) Subject: Re: MotifBC Reply-To: mccoy@gothamcity.jsc.nasa.gov Organization: I-NET Inc. X-Posted-From: krakatoa.jsc.nasa.gov NNTP-Posting-Host: sol.ctr.columbia.edu Lines: 15 In article h1m@vtserf.cc.vt.edu, stellr@smyrna.cc.vt.edu (Ray Stell) writes: |&gt; |&gt;If I install X11R5 with backward system compatibility for motif, will motif |&gt;1.2 clients work on the X11R5 servers? It works for me. I've run Motif 1.1.3,1.1.4,1.1.5,1.2,1.2.1, and 1.2.2 on an X11R5 server with MotifBC defined. --- Daniel J. McCoy |=&gt; SPACE &lt;=| I-NET, Inc. NASA Mail Code PT4 |=&gt; IS &lt;=| TEL: 713-483-0950 NASA/Johnson Space Center |=&gt; OUR &lt;=| FAX: 713-244-5698 Houston, Texas 77058 |=&gt; FUTURE &lt;=| mccoy@gothamcity.jsc.nasa.gov</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>8082</docid>
  <msgtext>From: GAnderson@Cmutual.com.au (Gavin Anderson) Subject: Help - Looking for a Medical Journal Article - Whiplash/Cervical Pain Lines: 37 Organization: Colonial Mutual Life Australia X-Newsreader: FTPNuz (DOS) v1.0 Lines: 24 Hi, I am not sure where to post this message, please contact me if I'm way off the mark. On 19.3.93 my wife went to her General Practitioner (Doctor). He mentioned an article from a medical journal that is of great interest to us. He had read it in the previous three months but has been unable to find it again. The article was about Whiplash Injury/Cervical Pain. It mentions the use of a MRI (Magnetic Resonance Imagery) machine as a diagnostic tool and the work of a neurosurgeon who relived cervical pain. This article is most likely in an Australian medical journal. I very much want to obtain the name of the article, journal and author because the case matches my wife. We would very much appreciate anyone's help in this matter via email preferably. --------------------------------------------------------------------------- Gavin Anderson email: GAnderson@cmutual.com.au Analyst/Programmer. phone: +61-3-607-6299 Colonial Mutual Life Aust. (ACN 004021809) fax : +61-3-283-1095 -----------Some people never consciously discover their antipodes---------- --------------------------------------------------------------------------- Gavin Anderson email: GAnderson@cmutual.com.au Analyst/Programmer. phone: +61-3-607-6299 Colonial Mutual Life Aust. (ACN 004021809) fax : +61-3-283-1095 ---------------------------------------------------------------------------</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>12869</docid>
  <msgtext>From: lvc@cbnews.cb.att.com (Larry Cipriani) Subject: Re: I believe in gun control. Organization: Ideology Busters, Inc. Lines: 22 In article &lt;1993Apr3.221837.2324@news.duc.auburn.edu&gt; bixledn@eng.auburn.edu writes: &gt;In article 16193@cbnews.cb.att.com, lvc@cbnews.cb.att.com (Larry Cipriani) writes: &gt;&gt; No, you haven't read it very closely . It says you may answer "No" if your &gt;&gt; civil rights have been restored; that can be done either by the feds' or a &gt;&gt; a state. I think the feds stopped doing this for those convicted of violent &gt;&gt; felonies. At least a dozen states still restore a felons civil rights, some &gt;&gt; immediately upon release, some after a waiting period. I will post a list &gt;&gt; of the states later. &gt;&gt; &gt; &gt; A quick question, then Larry, If a person's civil rights have been restored, &gt; then are they still considered a felon? Good question; I don't know what the law considers them. &gt; IMO, if rights have been restored, then it makes sense to me that the &gt; record of the felony, and everything else has been purged, and the &gt; person in question is no longer a felon. I believe this is what happens in some states. -- Larry Cipriani -- l.v.cipriani@att.com</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>17074</docid>
  <msgtext>From: rudy@netcom.com (Rudy Wade) Subject: Re: bob vesterman's plan to generate fan interest Organization: Home of the Brave Lines: 19 In article &lt;1254@rd1.interlan.com&gt; tonyf@rm1.interlan.com (Tony Fernandez) writes: &gt;The Marlins tried something like this and was a complete failure. On &gt;Opening Day, instead of having a 7th-inning stretch with the singing of &gt;Take Me Out to the Ballgame, they had some young women on the field lead &gt;the crowd into doing aerobics while the PA was playing Gloria Estefan's &gt;Get On Your Feet. The fans actually booed and started singing Take Me &gt;Out... on their own. I actually kind of felt sorry for the girls. Are you kidding? I'm stuck with the Toronto SkyDome, where their idea of a 7th inning stretch is that "Blue Jays" song where everyone gets to yell: "Okay, okay, Blue Jays, Blue Jays, Let's Play Ball!" Wow.. what genius did it take to compose that one, to outshine the old classic. And there are women on the field to "lead the crowd". Then again, this is the same crowd who is more entertained by the "grounds crew" and the word ground is used loosely, than it is by the outstanding plays by the opponents' fielders.</msgtext>
</doc>
<doc>
  <docid>6432</docid>
  <msgtext>From: earlw@apple.com (Earl Wallace) Subject: Re: "Proper gun control?" What is proper gun control? Distribution: usa Organization: Apple Computer Inc. ESD/OSBU/Cross-Platform Software Lines: 26 NNTP-Posting-Host: apple.com In article &lt;C5JAtz.5G4@cbnewsc.cb.att.com&gt; rats@cbnewsc.cb.att.com (Morris the Cat) writes: &gt;... &gt;Let's prohibit arms carrying by police when off-duty. Or, if they make &gt;the assertion that "Well, I need to maintain my gun" let's make it &gt;regulation that they can carry an UNLOADED firearm home, that it's &gt;only fair that they be just as helpless as poor schmuck coming home &gt;from his computer operator job... &gt; &gt;NRA Director/ex-San Jose cop Leroy Pyle states in the latest SWAT &gt;magazine that anti-cops better watch out for this schism between &gt;RKBA folks and the police. He asks the rhetorical question of 'What &gt;if what's left of the gun lobby starts demanding the disarmament &gt;of the police?" &gt; &gt;Well, I guess anti-gun cops who think only they should be armed, &gt;along with the wealthy and politically connected, should be made &gt;to realize that screwing can cut in ways they have yet to imagine. &gt;... We all know this will never happen. Because the Police are under the wings of Government, they will always be considered more important than Citizens. Government pens, pencils and paper are considered more important than Citizens. I think we have a problem with our Government.</msgtext>
</doc>
</root>
